STANDARD FOR LIFE
As wiseman Daniel moves along
The SCOAN prayer line ministering prayer
in the name of Jesus Christ,
see how the people move uncontrollably
as the Holy Ghost fire
begins to consume every power of darkness
in their lives,
for where the light of God is,
darkness has no hiding place.
See the reaction of this woman
as the contrary spirit inside of her
is exposed.
Fire in the mighty name of Jesus! Who are you?
Stop it!
Stop what?
Stop embarrassing me.
I am a journalist, I am the one who embarrasses people.
Okay!
You won't embarrass me!
You are a journalist?
I am the one who embarrasses people.
What do you mean by that?
I make fun of people who come here,
I write about them.
What are the things you say?
I make fun of the things they do and they say.
I am a journalist.
Nobody makes fun of me, I make fun of the people.
Stop this!
What have you done to her?
She is my wife now.
I married her long time ago.
I entered her through sexual abuse.
She was two and I made a mad neighbour to sleep with her
without the knowledge of her parents
for years.
What have you done to her marital life?
She is married to some Nigerian guy,
who is a soccer player.
I have frustrated his career.
He can't get a club in South Africa.
That thing!
I frustrated him.
He can't get a club.
He is not playing.
And everyone is making fun of him.
I am fine, wiseman.
Who is she to you?
She is my wife.
This one?
He is my driver.
He is what?
He used to be my gardener,
I promoted him to be my driver.
He used to be your gardener?
My gardener, yes.
I promoted him.
To what?
To a driver.
You are my driver.
You are my wife.
You know you are my driver,
you take me everywhere I want to go.
You are my wife.
This guy takes me everywhere I want to go,
I go to functions, he takes me there.
If I want to go to work, he takes me there.
I don't want to drive,
I refused to drive.
I have my own car, but I use his car.
I will never drive.
Who drives you?
My driver.
He said, he is your husband?
This?
I am an educated woman,
how can I marry a soccer player?
You mean he is not your husband?
A driver?
What is this drama? Cameras?
I am the one who writes gossip about people.
What is this thing now?
What does she do for a living?
She was a journalist but she stopped.
She is now a communication manager in a company.
And you said as a journalist you
make her to embarrass people
that come here.
What are the things that you make her to do?
She was a gossip writer, she wrote 'Page three'.
A gossip writer?
Yes.
What do you mean by that?
How does she do it?
She writes about celebrities.
If she sees a celebrity with a woman,
she exposes that.
Marriages have been broken because
of the stories she writes.
Listen, you make her to break marriages
because of the stories you make her to write?
She has written horrible stories about people.
She would see a man with another woman and write a story.
She doesn't drink alcohol,
she would be the only sobber person in a function.
She would be looking at what people are doing,
the following day - the story would be all over the papers.
What do you have to say about it?
Actually, what she is saying, she is a journalist.
She is a well known journalist in South Africa.
Sometimes she is into the 'Page three'.
'Page three' means people that write
controversial stories about celebrities
or government officials.
What she does - she goes and brings it out
on the pages
so people will always know about that.
So what are the things you said you write about people
coming to the Synagogue?
There is another time, I saw the celebrity on Emmanuel TV.
He confessed that he was having an affair with three women.
I wrote about that story and he was very embarrassed.
People who watch Emmanuel TV critised me.
What is the essence of writing stories about the people
that come here, what do you want to achieve?
I wanted to make fun, it was a good story.
I want to be the best.
What have you done to him?
This one?
I frustrate him.
What do you mean,
what are the things you have done to him?
I make his wife not to respect him.
I scatter his money.
The little money he gets from being a soccer coach
at one of those schools there - I scatter it
just to embarrass him.
What else have you done?
He got a nice, cushy job with the police in South Africa.
Guess what?
He only earned three salaries.
What did I do?
What do you mean by that?
They just told him that the
contract has been terminated.
There was a new commissioner
who did not what them anymore.
What have you done to his career as a footballer ?
Whose career?
This one?
He can't get a job, he can't get a club.
Why?
There was time, he wanted to play with a club.
You know what I did? I frustrated him.
He didn't get his clearance.
What can you say about her?
What she said about driving -
I paid for her to take the driving test
because before I wanted to come here ,
all my documents were stolen from my car.
Because I said to her that I wanted to come to The SCOAN,
and I wanted her to come too.
So my documents were all stolen.
What happened to his documents?
I stole them.
You stole them?
Yes.
Where did you take them to?
To some criminals.
Who made those people to come
and steal those documents?
I am the one.
What have you done to the marriage of this woman?
This guy can't enjoy his wife.
The wife hates kissing.
The wife hates sleeping with him.
The wife disrespects him.
The wife rules.
The wife earns more than him, she is the boss.
What can you say about that?
She is authoritative.
When I say her something, she will always argue before doing it.
She will always make sure she causes commotion.
And when she looks at you, she says she is just doing things because of...
What about the affection?
The affection - sometimes it's sour.
She tells me, she sees a spiritual husband in her dream,
after that dream, maybe for weeks,
we will not make love.
Right now it is time to leave this body.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
All over your body!
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Go!
In Jesus' name!
You are free, raise up!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Come!
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you, sir!
You said you are the spiritual husband.
No, he is my husband, sir.
He is your husband?
Yes, sir!
He is not your driver?
No.
Or your gardener?
No!
You said, he is your gardener and your driver.
No.
He is my husband.
He is the father of my children.
The confession that you heard is the
demon that was speaking through her,
right now that demon is out.
This is your true wife, okay?
Don't for any reason remind her of what happened here today
so that you also will not be tempted to do the same.
You are free.
Thank you, Jesus! We are free!
You listened to that?
There is something that the wisemen normally say
which I will remind you:
"Don't remind her no matter what happens in the house".
Whether the person is your wife, husband or friend
or even herself. That I have written about somebody -
that will constitute to attack.
When someone is delivered...
Viewers at home, if you watch Emmanuel TV
and you see your friend being delivered
and you are now using that in one way or another -
it's a great offense.
No matter what happens,
you can fight, you can abuse him or her differently -
not that thing he/she was delivered of.
If you dare mention that again...
Wow!
Unless you are delivered.
Because I don't know how you can get out of it,
unless you are delivered.
God is saying someone is free,
and you are now saying someone is not free.
Can you see, you are standing against God?
If am talking to you, let me see your hand.
It is God that has freed her.
When God says you are free,
someone is standing to say: "No!"
A man confesses that he has an evil spirit
and I say: "You are free in Jesus' name!" -
and the person is free immediately.
Now someone somewhere,
maybe in one way or the other they were fighting
and he says: "Ah, evil spirit."
You are telling God that the person is not delivered.
God says that the person is delivered and
you are saying that the person is not delivered.
And when you fight against God -
my God, you are finished!
So when the wiseman says:
"Don't ever repeat what you hear now,
no matter what happens in future."
Whether you people are fighting, or disagreement.
Whether you know the person somewhere
and you heard the confession they made.
And you are now using that
confession against the person.
God set the person free of that guilt -
and you are now saying: "No! He is not free."
It is the greatest offence.
Whether you are an apostle, or bishop
or prophet, or whatever name you call yourself -
I know that no anointed man would say such a thing,
because they know the position of God.
So this is a warning to the whole world.
Those who will continue to do it -
you will continue to see many of them
and I wish you good luck.
When you see somebody like this sister now, rejoice with her.
Because you too, you need deliverance.
Let's listen.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel!
My name is Nonyese John.
The man standing next to me is Namdi John.
I am a South African and he is a Nigerian.
We live in Johannesburg.
I am a journalist by profession
and he is a soccer player by profession.
The problem that brought us here was sickness.
I had a mild stroke and a spiritual husband.
When we came here, I wanted to be on the prayer line.
As a jounalist, you people are very out spoken.
I want you to be free and talk.
Before they touched you,
what was going through your mind?
Did you actually believe that what happened to you -
will happen to you?
Say everything, feel free.
Educate the whole world, as a journalist.
Because I have been prayed for before.
I have been prayed with powerful men of God before
breathing the same air with them.
I have been to Bible school just for fun anyway.
I have been with men of God before,
they have laid hands on me.
Nothing has ever happened to me like
what happened on that day.
In some instances, when the man of God is praying for me,
when people are falling -
I just fall because I feel sorry for him
because I didn't want him to be embarrassed.
Journalist, because they are the police of the world,
they will tell you what they feel.
She is telling us now that she has been to many places,
where she saw many people falling, she also fell
because she felt sorry for the man of God.
Because I didn't want the man of God to be embarrassed,
I just fell.
When wiseman Daniel came, I was very angry.
As I said, something else upset me, so I was just chilling.
As I was looking as the wiseman,
I was thinking: "He needs makeover".
I looked at his hair and stuff like that,
I even told my husband that the wiseman needs makeover.
My husband told me to concentrate on what we are here for
and stop talking about people.
When the wiseman touched me,
it was like I had been hit by something.
I've never had that experience before
in my life.
I went mad; the spirit in me went crazy,
I just wanted to run away,
I was so angry and uncomfortable.
I told him that I want to go back to South Africa.
As a celebrity journalist writing "Page three" and gossip,
I wrote about celebrities, politicians, men of God -
everyone who is in the lime light.
If they do something wrong, I will write about it.
If they cheat on their wives, I will write about it.
If they don't pay maintenance, I would write about that.
If they get drunk, I would write about that.
If they cheat, I would write about that.
I was one of the best "Page three" writers in South Africa.
People hated me, celebrities hated me,
I have been beaten up, followed around and threatened.
In September, I saw a South African
celebrity on Emmanuel TV.
The man of God prophesied that there
was a man in the congregation,
who had three girlfriends and was married
and the man was there.
I was shocked to see someone that I knew,
that I had written about before,
who is a well known business man and
a respected celebrity in South Africa.
I wrote that story.
I was told by the editors to call the man of God,
because if we mentioned anyone in the newspapers
in your story you have to get their comment.
I knew that it could have been silly to ask for a comment
like that from the man of God.
I went back to the editor and lied,
that I couldn't get the man of God.
But we carried on with the story anyway.
It was published on "Page three"
of the newspaper I used to work for.
Don't worry about the story. We thank God!
How are you feeling after your deliverance?
After my deliverance I went back to the internet,
I read the story that I had written -
I was so ashamed of myself.
I couldn't believe I could write some of the things I had wrote.
Can you tell us, when the wiseman laid the hand on you -
what actually happened to you?
The spirit inside of me was very angry.
I couldn't believe what was happening
and there were cameras all over the place
and there was a lady taking pictures of me.
I just went mad.
Ok, now as a journalist, what message
do you have to your colleagues all over the world?
Because it is always difficult for you to believe
and now you have seen -
what message do you have for them?
The message I have especially for my colleagues
journalists.
I had written some of the stories
that had been written about The SCOAN.
People must come here and experience for themselves.
They must not write hearsay.
This is a place of God;
God resides here.
I mean as I had said before, I have breathed
the same air with very powerful men of God.
I have gone to Bible school,
I have been with respected men of God.
But I have never experienced in my life
what I experienced that day.
Now, after you deliverance and after you went to lodge to sleep,
tell us your experience now.
How do you know you are free?
Compare the experience you are having now
and the experience you had in the past.
Since I was two, I have had
problem with a spiritual husband.
It would come in different forms;
I would be pressed at night.
I would be forced to sleep with my stomach
because I was scared that
that thing would press me until I die.
For the first time in my life I slept
peacefully with no problem.
Sometimes I would be prayed for, and I hoped
that the spiritual husband won't come back again.
But it comes back.
It has been for days I haven't experienced any problems.
I slept like a baby.
Hallelujah! You listen to that?
Your love towards your husband -
what about the affection?
Before then, I treated my husband like a friend,
like he was like one of the people - a brother.
But now we are more like husband and wife.
I love him more and everything is fine now.
OK, let's hear from my brother.
So how are you, my brother?
I am fine, daddy.
Now, that your wife has been delivered -
can you just give us in two minutes, before and after
- the affection?
Emmanuel!
Previously, I was staying with a man and a friend.
Sometimes, one or two experiences at home -
it was like two partners that are trying to compete
or to prove a point in the house.
But I believe after this deliverance
I have experienced a lot of differences.
I am so blessed and I am very
happy with this ministry.
Have you now recovered you wife
from the hands of the evil spirit?
Completely?
Totally!
Thank you! This is what we want to hear.
I hope you understood my question.
Because the person he married at the beginning -
there are many things he saw in the lady,
when he got married to her.
Now he has discovered those things,
those things were lost for sometime.
He has discovered those things.
Thank you very much!
Hallelujah!
Emmanuel TV
TT: Lizz Ndung'u
date : 10/9/2017
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 14/07/2018